<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Healthy Battery Charging</string>

    <string name="BatteryLevelNotifications">Battery level notifications</string>

    <string name="BatteryLowNotification">Battery low notification</string>
    <string name="BatteryHighNotification">Battery high notification</string>

    <string name="Low">Low:</string>
    <string name="High">High:</string>

    <string name="Save">Save</string>
    <string name="Reset">Reset</string>
    
    <string name="BatteryStatus">Battery status:</string>
    <string name="BatteryLevel">Battery level:</string>
    
    <string name="Charging">Charging</string>
    <string name="Discharging">Discharging</string>
    
    <string name="ConnectCharger">Connect the charger</string>
    <string name="DisconnectCharger">Disconnect the charger</string>
    
    <string name="MessageOK">
        You are all set! You will receive notifications indicating when to
        connect and disconnect the charger. Feel free to exit the app.
        \n\nAdditional notes on app functionality:
        \n\nThe app itself is optimized for low battery consumption, running in
        the background and checking the battery level every 15 minutes. The
        exact timing of these checks depends on the Android OS, which might
        schedule them alongside other tasks or delay them when in sleep mode.
        As a result, the battery level may slightly exceed the high threshold
        while charging or drop slightly below the low threshold while
        discharging before you receive a notification.
        \n\nThe app should continue running in the background after rebooting
        your phone. However, on certain devices, you may need to open the
        security settings and grant explicit permission for it to do so.
        \n\nCertain budget devices, especially older models with modifications
        to the operating system, terminate all background services when an app
        is removed from memory. If your device falls into this category, you
        will need to \'lock\' the app in memory to prevent this from happening.
        Additionally, ensure that the app is excluded from battery optimization.
    </string>
    <string name="MessageNOK">
        You are not set up yet! In order for the app to function properly, you
        need to grant it the necessary permissions. Please restart the app or
        go to your system settings and grant it notification permission.
    </string>

    <string name="DonationTitle">This app depends on your support</string>
    <string name="DonationContent">
        This app is free, open-source, and has no ads or trackers. To keep
        it that way, if you can, please donate today:
    </string>

</resources>
